Rediscover life and love.
Larry Crowne is a comedy, romance, drama film directed by Tom Hanks.
When he suddenly finds himself without his long-standing blue-collar job,
Larry Crowne enrolls at his local college to start over.
There, he becomes part of an eclectic community of
students and develops a crush on his teacher.
Larry Crowne, played by Tom Hanks.
Mercedes Tainot, played by Julia Roberts.
Dean Tainot, played by Bryan Cranston.
Lamar, played by Cedric the Entertainer.
Frances, played by Pam Grier.
B'Ella, played by Taraji P. Henson.
Larry Crowne is a 2011 American romantic comedy film
starring Tom Hanks and Julia Roberts.
The film was produced and directed by Hanks, who
co-wrote its screenplay with Nia Vardalos.
The story was inspired by Hanks' time studying at Chabot College.
The film tells the story of Larry Crowne, a middle-aged man who
unexpectedly loses his job and returns to education.
It was released in the United States on July 1, 2011.
The film explores themes of classroom, college, diner, teacher, love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.